[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the US Army, this rank is usually in charge of a battalion.", "correct_answer": "Lt. Colonel", "incorrect_answers": ["Brigadier General", "Captain", "Major General"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term lachanophobia means a fear of what?", "correct_answer": "vegetables", "incorrect_answers": ["beds", "doors", "llamas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2005 movie Water centered on people from this country.", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["Morocco", "China", "Chad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many different chemicals does a smoker inhale with one drag on the cigarette?", "correct_answer": "over 4000", "incorrect_answers": ["about 2000", "about 200", "between 500 and 1000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jennifer Lopez stars in this movie.", "correct_answer": "Shall We Dance", "incorrect_answers": ["Talk to Her", "Belle Epoque", "El"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Asian country did the Gado-gado salad originate?", "correct_answer": "Indonesia", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "China", "Thailand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Every day this number of species of plants and animals become extinct.", "correct_answer": "50 - 100", "incorrect_answers": ["140 - 200", "250 - 350", "10 - 20"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the following pairs (chat abbreviation - its  meaning) is wrong.", "correct_answer": "TTYL - To Tell You a Lie", "incorrect_answers": ["BRB - Be Right Back", "ATM - At The Moment", "TIA - Thanks In Advance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does Darth Vader wear his suit?", "correct_answer": "It keeps him alive.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "It gives him the power of the Force", "It id not revealed."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fastest animal on 6 legs?", "correct_answer": "Cockroach", "incorrect_answers": ["Ladybug", "Beetle", "Ant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Boons first name in the movie Animal House?", "correct_answer": "Donald", "incorrect_answers": ["Daniel", "David", "Dennis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many stomachs does a starfish have?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "0", "5"]}]